absolutecross.com 2001-06-06

# Privacy Policy -- Absolute Cross

**AbsoluteCross.com Privacy Policy**

**AbsoluteCross.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [AbsoluteCross.com](http://www.absolutecross.com/).

We may collect and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

This site, Absolute Cross - Graphics and Tips, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>.

Our site's registration forms pertaining to items such as guestbooks, forums, or mailing lists, etc., may require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our site company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **AbsoluteCross.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content, representations, or opinions of such Web sites.

Our site makes use of an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company or to improve our site. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We may occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

#### Public Forums

This site makes forums and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. AbsoluteCross.com does not take responsibily for claims, opinions, representations, or any other information in these areas that are beyond our control. Action will be taken in the case of misconduct in these areas.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@absolutecross.com](mailto:webmaster@absolutecross.com)
  2. To opt-out of a membership to the Absolute Cross Ezine, see this [form](http://www.absolutecross.com/ezine.htm). 

#### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@absolutecross.com](mailto:webmaster@absolutecross.com)

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact David Dunkerley Absolute Cross  3132 N. Ashwood St. Orange, CA 92865 [webmaster@absolutecross.com](mailto:webmaster@absolutecross.com)
